okay that is what bandhan bank but
Abhishek paytm gained over three percent
in trade on the back of its second
quarter business updates a lot of it
coming in uh tell us more about this and
what happened here
uh well the ticket sizes might have
increased as per my calculation so the
number of loans dispersed that's up
about 223 percentage on a yui basis and
about eight and a half percent
sequentially the value of lows dispersed
starts up almost 32 percent on a
sequential basis so if you take into
these two numbers and calculate the
average ticket size in terms of
dispersals is up about 80 percent yui
and about 21 and a half percent
sequentially the gross merchandise value
that's up more than 62 percent yui and
about seven and a half percent
sequentially the average MTU that is uh
you know uh is at eight crore up forty
point four percent YY and about six
point seven percent uh sequentially if
you calculate GMB uh per MTU it comes to
about thirty nine thousand seven fifty
rupees which is up uh fifteen point six
percent yui and about point seven
percent sequentially so the disbursers
are seeing an uptick in terms of ticket
sizes for paytm in Q2 f523 back to you
okay that is all about the bfsi space
moving on the union government